mytopfinding.com 2018-12-24

# Privacy Policy

This privacy policy statement is for mytopfinding.com only:

Mytopfinding.com collects some personal data (direct or indirect information that allows for the identification of a person) from you. And a third party, Rhapsody of Realities Influencers Distribution Partnership Platform, also collects some personal data from you when you visit their platform via a link from mytopfinding.com for their devotional. Other third party services such as **Google Analytics, AddToAny, YouTube, and Google AdSense  **collect usage data (non-personal data) from the applications you use to visit mytopfinding.com.

All data collected by us and our use of third party services enables the provision of the service required by you.

## Section 1 – Details

Here, you will find the types of data collected, why they are collected, and the places of storage and/or processing.

 **Contact**

You may freely provide us with your personal data (Name and email address) when you use our **contact form** or email us to communicate to us. You will not be able to use our contact form to communicate to us if you fail to fill out your name and email address. You authorize us to use your name and email address to reach you when responding to you. Our staff (located in Ghana) only stores your personal data to be used to get back to you.

 **Daily Devotional**

Our recommended Christian devotional platform, **Rhapsody of Realities Influencers Distribution Partnership Platform** , collects your name, email address, and other optional personal data when you fill out their form to download a free copy of their devotional. The link to their platform is provided on our page “[Get Your Rhapsody of Realities Daily Devotional](https://mytopfinding.com/get-your-rhapsody-of-realities-daily-devotional/)” (read their [Privacy Policy](https://rhapsodyofrealities.org/en/privacy-policy/)).

 **Analytics**

Google Analytics automatically collects your usage data (non-personal data); to track and examine any application used to visit mytopfinding.com, and to analyze user behavior. Google processes all usage data collected with Google Analytics in the United States (this is their [Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy) and [Opt Out](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en)).

 **Sharing Buttons**

We use AddToAny social media sharing buttons to help you share the content directly from the pages of this website with your friends and family on social media platforms. They collect your usage data (non-personal data), and they process them in the United States (you can read their [Privacy Policy](https://www.addtoany.com/privacy)). Note that whatever you share from any of our pages is subject to your privacy settings on any of the social media platforms.

 **Video Embeds**

Mytopfinding.com, on some pages, use videos hosted on the external platform “YouTube.” YouTube collects usage data (non-personal data), and your data processing is done in the United States (read their [Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy)).

 **Advertisements**

Google AdSense may serve ads and collect some anonymous data when you visit mytopfinding.com. They use the contexts of our content and/or your usage (non-personal) data to provide relevant advertisements that may benefit you. They use cookies (small sets of data stored in your device by mytopfinding.com and/or any third party) or web beacon to collect your usage data. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice you can visit [Networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

Note carefully here: Google does not use personal data to provide advertisements. And mytopfinding.com will not use your personal data for marketing purposes.

## Section 2 – Consent and Retention Time Of Personal Data

You consent that we store your name and email address to be used to respond back to you when you use our contact form or email us; we may also store any other personal data you provide during your communication with us.

And mytopfinding.com will keep your personal data as long as you do not withdraw your consent. During which the purpose they have been collected for may be fulfilled. We may be obliged to keep your personal data for a much longer time than your consented period when required to fulfill an order of a law or authority.

## Section 3 – You Have Rights

You have the right to contact us to withdraw your consent at any time, verify the accuracy of your data, or have it removed from our storage. Mytopfinding.com does not support “Do Not Track” requests, but you can find out whether any of the third parties listed in SECTION – 1 uses it or not.

## Section 4 – Security and Disclosure

Mytopfinding.com takes all security measures to prevent unauthorized disclosure, access, and destruction of the name and email address you provide using our contact form. But by consenting (SECTION – 2), you declare your awareness that mytopfinding.com may be required by law to reveal your personal data when public authorities request for it.

## Section 5 – Modifications to This Privacy Policy

Mytopfinding may, at any time, make changes to this privacy policy; and you will only know of it when you visit this website, especially, this page (always check the last updated date at the bottom of this page to give you a clue if there are any changes).

Use our [contact form](https://mytopfinding.com/contact/) to reach us

Mytopfinding is the data controller

Last update: November 12, 2018
